Did
you
know
your
pineapple
has
trust
issues
Because
it
takes
a
year
and
a
half
to
three
years
just
to
grow
one
Thats
commitment
issues
in
fruit
form
Weird
facts
you
definitely
didnt
learn
in
school
Hip
hose
Yeah
They
basically
sweat
blood
Except
its
not
blood
Its
just
red
and
confusing
Thanks
nature
Hedgehogs
can
run
for
miles
per
hour
Thats
faster
than
your
Wi
Fi
during
a
Zoom
call
The
phrase
hands
down
isnt
about
being
chill
Its
from
horse
racing
A
jockey
so
far
ahead
He
can
literally
drop
the
reins
and
still
win
Now
thats
confidence
The
Stripe
Skunk
scientific
name
is
Mufitis
which
translates
to
stinky
No
notes
Perfect
name
The
New
England
coast
is
crawling
with
cats
who
have
extra
toes
Theyre
called
polydactyl
cats
Sailors
believe
they
were
good
luck
So
they
brought
them
aboard
ships
Basically
cats
were
the
OG
good
luck
charms
With
bonus
toes
Only
female
wass
can
sting
The
males
are
just
out
here
buzzing
around
being
useless
in
fights
like
some
exes
we
know
Twinkies
were
originally
filled
with
banana
cream
until
World
War
II
said
no
more
bananas
for
you
So
they
switched
to
vanilla
and
people
liked
it
so
much
banana
never
came
back
RIP
banana
Twinkie
And
finally
ants
You
thought
your
Penderesca
was
cool
Ants
were
farming
fungus
before
humans
figured
out
how
to
plant
corn
Thats
right
Farmer
ants
With
tiny
hats
Okay
not
really